ILGWU. Upper South Department records 5780/039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 393, Westminster, Maryland, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Local 400, Roanoke, Virginia, 1944-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Resignations [Locals 400 and 413], 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Local 402, Bristol, Virginia, 1946-1950 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Local 406, Arlington, Virginia, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Local 416, Clarksburg, West Virginia, 1947-1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Local 419, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1944-1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Local 328, Kokomo, Indiana, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Local 420, Huntington, West Virginia [folder 1 of 4], 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Local 420, Huntington, West Virginia [folder 2 of 4], 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Local 420, Huntington, West Virginia [folder 3 of 4], 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Local 420, Huntington, West Virginia [folder 4 of 4], 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Local 420, Huntington, W. Va., 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  flyers and leaflets
- Local 420, Huntington, W. Va., 1942-1953 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Local 420, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Local 422. Pt. Pleasant, W. Va., 1947-1954 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  April 28, 1947-Feb. 3, 1954. Minutes of Local meetings.
- Local 422. 1945-60. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Local 425. Martinsburg, W. Va., 1942-1955 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Local 425, 1946-1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Perfection Garment Co.
- Local 425, 1950-1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Materials used in organizing work.
- Local 425, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Newspaper clippings re strike against Perfect Garment Co.
- Local 430. Martinsville, W. Va., 1945-1947 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Local 430, 1945-1948 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Circulars and leaflets, incl. "The Button-Hole News," 1948.
- Local 430, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Incl. monthly financial statements.
- Local 434. Cumberland, Md., 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  I.c.w. David Dubinsky re unauthorized strike, 1946.
- Local 435. Hagerstown, Md., 1945-1949 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Local 438. Winchester, Va., 1942-1951 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Local 464. Buchanan, Va., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Minutes of membership meetings.
- Local 424. Marion, Va. [folder 1 of 4], 1946-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Incl. Wilburn Steele case and GEB appeal.
- Local 424. Marion, Va. [folder 2 of 4], 1946-1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Local 424. Marion, Va. [folder 3 of 4], 1946-1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Local 424. Marion, Va. [folder 4 of 4], 1946-1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Local 504. Crewe, Va., 1950-1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Local 561. Bedford, Va., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Incl. records of paid strike benefits.
- Local 585. Cambridge, Md., 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Membership meeting minutes.
- M, 1942-1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Medical Health Center, Baltimore, Md. ( n.d. ) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Circulars, brochures.
- Mental Health, 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Incl. corres. re involvement of Union in mental health needs of community.
- Milano, Edward, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Myles Mfg. Co., 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Estate of L.V. Myles; incl. corres. re negotiations.
- N, 1944-1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1943-1962 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Corres. re cases arranged alphabetically by firm.
- NLRB, 1946-1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Corres. and circulars.
- Northeast Dept, 1944-1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- O, 1943-1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1956-1966 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Philip Camp, 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Leon Deane, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Samuel Einhorn, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Whiting C. Faulkner, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Robert Gladnick [folder 1 of 4], 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Robert Gladnick [folder 2 of 4], 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Robert Gladnick [folder 3 of 4], 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Robert Gladnick [folder 4 of 4], 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Sol Goldberg, 1950-1951 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Organizers and Business Agents. William Goldsmith, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Organizers and Business Agents. William Kaufman [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1953 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Incl. corres. as Virginia State Director.
- Organizers and Business Agents. William Kaufman [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1953 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Jessie Kozma, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Myrtle Lee, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Joe Lewis [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1949 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Joe Lewis [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1949 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Grace McWhorter, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Organizers and Business Agents. John MacKensie, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Eliot Meyers, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Ruth Murray, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Jean Martin Pagano [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Incl. corres. as educational director.
- Organizers and Business Agents. Jean Martin Pagano [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Jules Pagano, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Joseph E. Pearce, 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Carrie Riggs, 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Mabel Roten, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Abe Safir, 1946-1949 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Charles Tillman, 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Mildred Volz [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Mildred Volz [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Saul Zivian [folder 1 of 4], 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Saul Zivian [folder 2 of 4], 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Saul Zivian [folder 3 of 4], 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Organizers and Business Agents. Saul Zivian [folder 4 of 4], 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Organizing. Leaflets and circulars. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Organizing. Leaflets and circulars. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Organizing. Leaflets and circulars. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Organizing. Leaflets and circulars, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Incl. Rutledge organizing drive (1952)
- Our Kids, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Pub. on adoption of children.
- P, 1942-1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  I.c.w. Abraham Plotkin re Reliance negotiations.
- Political Dept., Upper South, 1950-1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Gus Tyler.
- Political Dept., Upper South. (n.d.) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Leaflets and lists of members for political purposes.
- Politics. Campaigns, 1940-1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Corres., leaflets and circulars during presidential elections.
- Politics. Campaigns, 1950-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Corres., leaflets and circulars during state and local elections.
- Politics. Congressional and Senatorial Letters [folder 1 of 3], 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Politics. Congressional and Senatorial Letters [folder 2 of 3], 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Politics. Congressional and Senatorial Letters [folder 3 of 3], 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Price Settlements [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Price Settlements [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1949 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- R, 1946-1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Radio Scripts [folder 1 of 3], 1941-1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Radio Scripts [folder 2 of 3], 1941-1964 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Radio Scripts [folder 3 of 3], 1941-1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Resignations, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  July 1946. Resignations of six organizers; i.c.w. David Dubinsky.
- Resignations, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Signed resolutions protesting resignations sent out by Miriam Billings, Local 239
- Resignations, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Ltrs. from Union members re resignations
- Retirement Fund, Baltimore Jt. Bd. and Upper South Dept., 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Corres. and agreements with employers re establishment of Retirement Fund; data on employees
- S, 1942-1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- St. Paul, Va. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Corres. re organizing Jacobs Plant.
- St. Paul, Va. [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Shane, Joe [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Asst. mgr., Upper South Dept.; i.c.w. Maida Springer re Southern Rhodesia.
- Shane, Joe [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Shane, Joe [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Southeastern Region [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Southeastern Region [folder 2 of 2], 1942-1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Strikes, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Farmville Dress strike.
- Strikes [folder 1 of 2], 1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  June 1965. Classic Uniform, Keyes Baker, Barclay Uniform.
- Strikes [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Stulberg, Louis [folder 1 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Stulberg, Louis [folder 2 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Stulberg, Louis [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- T, 1945-1959 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Tyler, Gus, 1963-1966 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- U, 1942-1951 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Unions, non-ILGWU, 1945-1958 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Incl. corres. re inter-union disputes with District 50, United MineWorkers.
- Upper South Dept., 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Conferences.
- Upper South Dept., 1948 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Upper South Dept., 1949 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Upper South Dept., 1950 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Upper South Dept., 1951 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Upper South Dept., 1952 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Upper South Dept., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Upper South Dept., 1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Upper South Dept., 1963 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Upper South Dept. ( n.d.) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  Conferences; resolutions.
- V-W, 1945-1969 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Women's Day, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- World War II, 1942-1945 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Corres. with Union members in military service.
- X-Y-Z, 1940-1951 (Box 22, Folder 14)